{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775028864","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775028864"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775065242","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775065242"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775067979","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775067979"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775101678","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775101678"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775127528","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775127528"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775130035","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775130035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775156464","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775156464"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775160123","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775160123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775186470","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775186468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775186578","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775186578"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543775204472","data":{"timestamp":" 1543775204472"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181202_212308"," gameId":" 1c04c346-4625-482c-a28a-a8e25bc4d0f6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}